Dragon...
Smash!
Whoa, awesome!
I-I did it!
You just have to store up spirit, hone it,
give it a "hiyah," and then go "bang!"
Man, I'm surprised you pulled
it off based on that, Clay.
Sophie!
Do you want to learn how to use it, too?
No need to be shy!
Yeah.
You just store up spirit, hone it, give
it a "gyuwawah," and then go "boom!"
Huh?
That's not what he said.
Wait, really?
Dragon Smash.
What's going on?!
Well, this is what Dragon Smash
is supposed to look like.
Seriously?!
Clay's was so wimpy!
You're really amazing, Sophie.
It took me so many days to get it.
Everyone, get away from her.
What?!
Blade.
This is my battle to fight.
I'll protect you.
Th-There are two Sophies?!
Wh-What's the meaning of this?!
A duplication technique?
Dragon Smash.
What was that?
Beats me.
I look in your eyes, and I'm met with
A brand-new me and dream
Bravery? Naturally?
Polar opposites within the heart
But, you know, wanting to have both
That's the saga of human nature
Oh no, don't mind me
Go ahead, and so on, you know the rest
A little more? Wait, even harder?!
Going overboard much?
Those selfish emotions deep down
Bringing them to light is
what friendship's about
Spending adolescence duking it out with pals
I don't wanna lose
We're off to the cutting edge moment
Fight with best friends, and leave no regrets
You should laugh, since
you look best with a smile
On the ropes?! No matter
what we face, et cetera
Just sit back and enjoy it
Whatever may come, I'll
be here to protect you
Episode 11
The Sophie Series (Part 1)
I'm back.
Une must have failed her mission.
Yo, you can't be serious!
What a pain! Let's just go in guns blazing,
and kill everyone in sight!
C'mon, it's killing time!
Une.
Did you find anyone cute worth killing?
Destroy! Destroy!
This was an undercover scouting mission,
in order to assess the situation.
In that regard, it was a success.
You really did fail the mission.
Your lack of proof just confirms it...
Une can't do anything.
So useless...
Cinq.
You have permission to destroy.
Destroy! Destroy!
Time to destroy Trois!
It hurts!
So, what was the outcome?
I had them teach me.
Huh?
Be a little clearer.
It's hard to explain with just words.
In that case...
Transmitting empirical data through
mucosal contact is certainly useful.
Deux.
Huh?
It hurts!
Destroy!
I said it hurts, jackass!
Come here, Trois.
You too, Cinq.
Huh? What was your goal here?
Like I said, I had them teach me.
Dragon Smash.
Dragon Smash!
You know this isn't our goal.
Totally not!
What we were commanded to do...
Assassination! Assassination!
Yes. You're absolutely right.
What are you about to show us?
Just be quiet and watch!
Here I go!
Eliza, this is incredible!
It's still a prototype,
but it looks like it worked!
So, which part of that was impressive?
All it did was fire off some
stored-up spirit over and over.
I don't need the opinion of a superorganism
who can hone and store his spirit
all by himself!
That's hard for us regular human beings!
It's hard, huh?
However!
By honing spirit and charging
it up into these cartridges,
now anyone can activate it at
any time that they see fit!
I get it now.
Blade.
Oh, she's here.
What do you want to learn?
How to make babies?
Eh?
You know that's not happening!
Then...
How I can kill you!
I'm fine with that.
You are?
Time to die, then!
Sure. Come at me!
I can't kill you!
Do a better job teaching me!
What?!
But if I actually teach you,
I'll end up dead!
Then...
Kill me instead.
Hey, Sophie!
What?!
Th-That's...
S-Sophie?!
Ah, Sophie.
Just when we were getting to the good part.
I'm the one you're up against.
Well, bye now.
How many does that make?
First, the one with a sword.
After that, a club, then a spear...
So this is the fourth?
Here, open wide.
Ahh!
Hey, what do you think is
the deal with those girls?
I'm not sure, but they're good learners.
Yeah, they're really passionate.
I wouldn't call it passion...
Do you think they're Sophie's sisters?
They should all just enroll in the academy.
Hold on, Anna.
Let's think this through a bit.
Don't you find it at least a little weird?
Huh?
You've become a lot like Blade lately.
In your lack of common sense, that is.
Ahem.
Do you have anything to say about the
unusual situation we find ourselves in?
She's gone into Empress mode.
Um...
Do you mind if I say something?
Go ahead.
Well...
From an outside perspective,
it seems clear to me...
that those girls are seriously
trying to kill Blade!
I do the same thing when
I attack him during lessons.
Me, too!
If anything, I'd finish him off.
Don't forget that I'm the
one who will kill him.
What?! Um, sorry!
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
Lay off her already.
Can't you see that she's scared?
Am I being scolded by Blade?!
BA-DUMP
Um, I didn't mean it in
the way that you all do.
Pretending to be Sophie to get close to him...
Attacking him with clear murderous intent...
That has to be...
Um, give me a second here.
The most probable conclusion we can
arrive at from all of these facts is...
that Blade is being targeted by assassins!
Sophie!
What's wrong?
I just found out that none of you
realized that they were assassins.
Wait! D-Don't worry!
We knew all along! We really did!
I had it figured out from the start.
Act a little scared about it, then!
Is someone after your life, Parent?
It's fine.
I'll protect Blade.
You all failed!
It's me next!
I'll destroy! Destroy!
Can I destroy him?
Shut your trap.
You're giving me a headache.
I haven't failed yet.
That must be it.
The lack of proof just confirms it.
The Great Hero couldn't kill me.
That means I can kill him next time, right?
Destroy, destroy!
Be quiet.
Destroy everything!
Wasting unnecessary energy
will only shorten your lifespan.
Une.
Deux. Trois.
Quatre.
Cinq.
It's up to you to show everyone
that an Artificial Great Hero can
surpass even the Great Hero himself.
Kill the Great Hero Blade,
and prove the validity of our research.
We understand.
That is the sole reason that
we were brought to life.
We're the strongest!
Is that you, Sophie?
Yes.
Please deactivate your stealth.
It makes it difficult to
detect you with my sensors.
I don't want to wake Blade up.
Are you worried about Master?
There is no need to worry.
I am always by his side.
Would you like to sleep next to him as well?
Now is your chance to do so
as much as you like.
No, thanks.
Please leave it to me.
I will protect Master with my life.
I'll do what I can to protect Blade, too.
Even if it means death.
Give up.
You can't kill Blade.
We won't let you.
No, we will.
That is what we were commanded to do,
and the only purpose of our lives.
The Artificial Great Hero Project was
abandoned, with me as the final subject.
The modifications you received did
not follow the proper procedure.
That must have had a considerable
impact on your bodies.
I know that.
We have very short lifespan,
unlike you.
Instead of using the limited time
left to you to obey commands,
can't you live as humans,
and spend it in the light of day?
Our orders are absolute.
If you want to stop us...
There's only one way.
Deep down, I'm sure you've realized it, too.
We'll be waiting.
In our world, where the
light of day does not reach.
Sophie is pint-sized today!
Cinq!
Hm?
My name is Cinq!
Not Sophie!
So they have their own names.
I believe that Cinq is an ancient lost word
that signifies the number five.
Are there only five of you?
Is it okay for you to tell us that?
It wasn't!
Well, I don't think she could have
pretended to be Sophie if she tried.
Forget I said that!
Or else I'll destroy you!
Okay, okay!
I forgot it!
Good, good.
But I'm still gonna destroy you!
Hey, Blade!
Stick to the plan!
I know I should!
Destroy! Destroy! Destroy!
Not even a superorganism
can withstand that...
Destroy! Destroy! Destroy!
Blade.
C'mon, wake up.
How long are you going to stay dead?
He finally woke up!
Master won every exercise
that took place in virtual reality.
He is unaccustomed to dying.
Where's Cinq?!
She left already.
In an extremely good mood, at that.
I don't think she realized she had
been led into virtual reality.
So, if she's convinced that she
killed Mr. Superorganism,
our plan is a success!
I just hope she doesn't find out.
I know, right?
If she does...
You tricked me!
Destroy! Destroy! Destroy! Destroy!
Lemme destroy you!
I knew that's how she'd react!
Destroy! Destroy! Destroy!
Whoa, she's pissed!
Academy Building No. 2 is at 30% damage.
Any more damage carries the risk of collapse,
so I propose that we relocate to Building
No. 3, which has been fully evacuated.
Well, tell her that!
I'm sure she wouldn't listen!
I can kill him, right?!
Right?!
I'm here to kill you, so stop running!
Destroy! Destroy! Destroy!
I will proceed to steer them.
Leave it to me.
Yo momma's got a big ol' outie!
What's that mean?
It is a phrase used to taunt
others in a lost ancient language.
Unfortunately, its meaning has
been deleted from my records.
It worked!
Here they come!
It's up to all of you!
Understood!
But, Altia...
Are we really strong enough to defeat them?
We messed up during our last exam...
Can we really do it?
Well...
You'll be fine.
It's okay if you don't want to kill anyone.
They're on the same level as Sophie.
Launch your spells at them,
and don't hold back!
Yes!
You've got this!
Fire!
Blade, you can also use magic?
Hm? A little.
Now is your chance to take them alive.
What? That wasn't enough?!
Artificial Great Hero Power!
You'd better stand back.
Eh?
Master.
That is a black hole.
I propose that we withdraw immediately.
Otherwise...
Hold out for ten seconds!
You think it's over? No way.
Destroy! Destroy! Destroy!
Once a black hole has formed,
it will not die out by itself.
What?!
Okay, what now?
Altia!
Sophie!
Artificial Great Hero Power.
Ten. Nine. Eight.
Seven. Six.
Five. Four.
Three... Two...
One...
You did well, Sophie.
Blade...
Oh, you're awake?
You're supposed to cut
them like rabbits, right?
Did I get it right?
You're right about the rabbits.
But wrong about how you cut them.
Huh? I'm not supposed to use this?
Any casualities?
Ah, no one died.
A few people were injured,
but it's okay, since Claire
healed them in time.
And I just got a few scrapes.
I see.
Sorry for causing so much trouble.
We're all fine with it, so no worries.
Can you tell me about them?
Those girls... are me.
Specimens created with the same cloning
technology, with further modifications...
and successfully manifested
Artificial Great Hero powers
after receiving implants
of the rare metal Heronium.
They've been given numbers,
so I feel like that must be the case.
You mean the Artificial Great Hero Project?
I was rescued by the king,
but those girls didn't
have anyone to help them.
I met you at this academy,
and made friends with everyone.
You were my salvation.
You're the one who saved me.
You've suffered so much, all because
of the Great Hero's powers.
And yet you forgave me, the Great Hero.
I already told you.
I take pride in these powers of mine.
I never once resented you.
I want to be friends with them, too.
Earnest suggested that all five of
them should enroll in this school.
That can't happen.
Huh?
The Artificial Great Heroes were born to
defeat the Great Hero... that is, you.
Their sole purpose in life is to surpass you.
I was rescued before any
neural modifications,
so I wasn't programmed as such...
but those girls can't disobey their orders.
And besides...
The sunny disposition that
brings a smile to your face
As well as the heroic sense of justice
They may be a part of me,
but that's not all there is
That image of me
Has taken on a life of its own
Hey, wait up
Won't you be friends with me?
Let's shake hands, another self of mine
The wounds we cannot bear alone
The dangers that we keep hidden
We're all hiding them within
Standing ready to strike
The shadow lurking beneath the light
The muffled sounds coming from my lips
They make me feel that I am alive
It's a sign
Next Time
The Sophie Series (Part 2)